<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>XU LAB</title>
    <link>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on XU LAB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 12:14:25 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cmaorx.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The second term of “Famous National Doctor”.</title>
      <link>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 12:14:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>Professor Xu Ruihua was awarded the second term of “Famous National Doctor” The Second National Famous Doctors Summit, sponsored by People&amp;rsquo;s Daily and Health Times, was held in Beijing People&amp;rsquo;s Daily. Professor Xu Ruihua, Director and Dean of CancerControl Center of Sun Yat-sen University, was awarded the honorary title of &amp;ldquo;National Doctor, Outstanding Style&amp;rdquo;. Prof. Lu Taixiang, Senior</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New breakthroughs</title>
      <link>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/post/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 11:03:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/post/post1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;A team of Chinese, Japanese and Korean researchers led by Professor Xu Ruihua of Sun Yat-sen University&amp;rsquo;s Cancer Hospital conducted a large-scale, multi-center, phase III clinical trial of patients with advanced colorectal cancer after failed first-line treatment, AXEPT Research (Study No. NCT01996306) Objective To investigate the efficacy and tolerance of the modified double-drug combination scheme ( capecitabine+ irinotecan, XELIRI for short).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about us</title>
      <link>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 17:00:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/page/about/</guid>
      <description>p{text-indent: 1cm}  
 Brief Introduction of the Leader of the Task Force    Xu Ruihua, M.D. ( M.D. ), Ph. D.).Director of the cancer prevention and treatment center of Sun Yat-sen University;baijie, the new century talents of the Ministry of Education, Member of the Department of Biology and Medicine of the Science and Technology Commission of the Ministry of Education, vice president of the Chinese Society of Clinical Oncology ( CSCO ), and vice director of the China Medical Biotechnology Association chairman of the Guangdong Anti-Cancer Association, chairman of the targeted therapy Committee of the China Anti-Cancer Association, and the chemotherapy section of the large intestine cancer committee of the China Anti-Cancer Associationteam leader,Journal Of Chief editor of cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018article</title>
      <link>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/publication/2018article/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 14:59:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/publication/2018article/</guid>
      <description>Cell Res Feng Wang, Dong-Bing Liu, Qi Zhao, Gang Chen, Xin-Ming Liu, Ying-Nan Wang, Hong Su, Yan-Ru Qin, Yi-Fu He, Qing-Feng Zou, Yan-Hui Liu, You-En Lin, Ze-Xian Liu, Jin-Xin Bei, Rui-Hua Xu The genomic landscape of small cell carcinoma of the esophagus.In Cell Res. 2018 May 4. Cancer Res Yun-Xin Lu, Huai-Qiang Ju, Ze-Xian Liu, Dong-Liang Chen, Yun Wang, Qi Zhao, Qi-Nian Wu, Zhao-lei Zeng, Hai-Bo Qiu, Pei-Shan Hu, Zhi-Qiang</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/page/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 09:58:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/page/people/</guid>
      <description>#bbb{ Background-color:#000; }</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONTACT</title>
      <link>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cmaorx.github.io/en/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>P{background-color: #EAEAEA} E-mail :bioinfo@sysucc.org.cn &amp;nbsp; Address: Yuexiu district of Guangzhou City, Guangdong Province, Dongfeng East Road No. 651</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>